The enchanting story of a small boy who inherits an earldom
Little Lord Fauntleroy is a family, drama, tv movie film directed by Jack Gold.
Young Cedric Errol and his widowed mother live in genteel poverty
in 1880s Brooklyn after the death of his father.
Cedric's grandfather, the Earl of Dorincourt, has long ago
disowned his son for marrying an American.
But after the death of the Earl's remaining son, he
decides to accept Cedric as his heir.
Cedric Errol / Lord Fauntleroy, played by Rick Schroder.
Earl of Dorincourt, played by Alec Guinness.
Mr. Havisham, played by Eric Porter.
Silas Hobbs, played by Colin Blakely.
Mrs. Errol, played by Connie Booth.
Lady Lorradaile, played by Rachel Kempson.
Little Lord Fauntleroy is a 1980 British family drama television film directed by Jack Gold and adapted
by Blanche Hanalis from Frances Hodgson Burnett's 1886 children's novel of the same name.
The film stars Sir Alec Guinness, Rick Schroder, Eric
Porter, Connie Booth, and Colin Blakely.
The tone is emotional.